[
  {
    "id": 0,
    "text": "Marissa Mayer announced a new edge computing at SpaceX.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Marissa Mayer",
        "PERSON"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 1,
    "text": "Apple released a quantum computing that improves edge computing.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Apple",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "text": "Records show battle happened in Rome, Italy around 1664-06-18.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Rome",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Italy",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "1664-06-18",
        "DATE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "text": "Kamala Harris met leaders from Congress in Geneva, Switzerland to discuss policy announcement.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Kamala Harris",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "Congress",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "Geneva",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Switzerland",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "text": "Max Planck Institute announced a particle discovery that impacts genetics.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Max Planck Institute",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "text": "A study on particle discovery led by Isaac Newton was published on 1991-04-05.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Isaac Newton",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "1991-04-05",
        "DATE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "text": "Cristiano Ronaldo led Wimbledon to victory at the season opener in Melbourne, Australia.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Cristiano Ronaldo",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "Wimbledon",
        "EVENT"
      ],
      [
        "Melbourne",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Australia",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "text": "George Washington Carver led trials of yield improvement study in Punjab, India.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "George Washington Carver",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "Punjab",
        "NORP"
      ],
      [
        "India",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "text": "Barack Obama announced policy changes regarding education at Washington, USA.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Barack Obama",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "Washington",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "USA",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "text": "Angela Merkel met leaders from Parliament in New Delhi, India to discuss policy announcement.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Angela Merkel",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "Parliament",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "New Delhi",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "India",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "text": "Angela Merkel announced policy changes regarding healthcare at Geneva, Switzerland.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Angela Merkel",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "Geneva",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Switzerland",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "text": "CIMMYT introduced a yield improvement study to improve yields in Iowa, USA.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "CIMMYT",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "Iowa",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "USA",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "text": "restructuring led to restructuring at Goldman Sachs.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Goldman Sachs",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "text": "Leonardo da Vinci premiered a symphony at Vienna, Austria.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Leonardo da Vinci",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "Vienna",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Austria",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 14,
    "text": "M.S. Dhoni led Wimbledon to victory at the season opener in London, UK.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "M.S. Dhoni",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "Wimbledon",
        "EVENT"
      ],
      [
        "London",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "UK",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 15,
    "text": "CERN announced a field research that impacts biology.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "CERN",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 16,
    "text": "Tesla opened a new office in Frankfurt, Germany to expand manufacturing.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Tesla",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "Frankfurt",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Germany",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 17,
    "text": "Sundar Pichai became CEO of Tesla following the acquisition.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Sundar Pichai",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "Tesla",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 18,
    "text": "A breakthrough in robotics was reported by Apple.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Apple",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 19,
    "text": "AgriTech Ltd introduced a irrigation technique adoption to improve yields in Iowa, USA.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "AgriTech Ltd",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "Iowa",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "USA",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 20,
    "text": "Researchers at Harvard University reported a particle discovery in Cape Town, South Africa.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Harvard University",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "Cape Town",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "South Africa",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 21,
    "text": "Barack Obama met leaders from United Nations in Washington, USA to discuss policy announcement.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Barack Obama",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "United Nations",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "Washington",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "USA",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 22,
    "text": "Kamala Harris announced policy changes regarding trade at Geneva, Switzerland.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Kamala Harris",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "Geneva",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Switzerland",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 23,
    "text": "FC Barcelona announced a new tournament for 2024-2025.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Barcelona",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "2024-2025",
        "DATE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 24,
    "text": "Sundar Pichai announced a new quantum computing at SpaceX.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Sundar Pichai",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 25,
    "text": "CERN announced a field research that impacts climatology.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "CERN",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 26,
    "text": "Vincent van Gogh premiered a exhibition at Madrid, Spain.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Vincent van Gogh",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "Madrid",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Spain",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 27,
    "text": "A study on particle discovery led by Jane Goodall was published on 1500-11-03.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Jane Goodall",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "1500-11-03",
        "DATE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 28,
    "text": "Samsung opened a new office in Seoul, South Korea to expand manufacturing.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Samsung",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "Seoul",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "South Korea",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 29,
    "text": "Intel released a robotics that improves 5G networks.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Intel",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "5",
        "CARDINAL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 30,
    "text": "restructuring led to restructuring at Tesla.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Tesla",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 31,
    "text": "Kamala Harris met leaders from Congress in Washington, USA to discuss policy announcement.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Kamala Harris",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "Congress",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "Washington",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "USA",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 32,
    "text": "NBA announced a new season opener for 2023-2024.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "NBA",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "2023-2024",
        "DATE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 33,
    "text": "M. S. Swaminathan led trials of pest control trial in Lima, Peru.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "M. S. Swaminathan",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "Lima",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Peru",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 34,
    "text": "Barack Obama announced policy changes regarding climate at Geneva, Switzerland.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Barack Obama",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "Geneva",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Switzerland",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 35,
    "text": "Barack Obama met leaders from Parliament in Washington, USA to discuss policy announcement.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Barack Obama",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "Parliament",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "Washington",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "USA",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 36,
    "text": "A famous opera by Vincent van Gogh is housed in Tate Modern in Madrid, Spain.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Vincent van Gogh",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "Tate Modern",
        "FAC"
      ],
      [
        "Madrid",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Spain",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 37,
    "text": "Satya Nadella led the launch of a AI-driven sensors in Silicon Valley, USA.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Satya Nadella",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "AI",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Silicon Valley",
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        "USA",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 38,
    "text": "Sundar Pichai became CEO of Reliance Industries following the acquisition.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Sundar Pichai",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "Reliance Industries",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 39,
    "text": "Researchers at Max Planck Institute reported a field research in Geneva, Switzerland.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Max Planck Institute",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "Geneva",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Switzerland",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 40,
    "text": "Sundar Pichai became CEO of Tesla following the acquisition.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Sundar Pichai",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "Tesla",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 41,
    "text": "International Rice Research Institute introduced a yield improvement study to improve yields in Punjab, India.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "International Rice Research Institute",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "Punjab",
        "NORP"
      ],
      [
        "India",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 42,
    "text": "A study on climate study led by Albert Einstein was published on 1771-02-18.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Albert Einstein",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "1771-02-18",
        "DATE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 43,
    "text": "Wangari Maathai led trials of irrigation technique adoption in Lima, Peru.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Wangari Maathai",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "Lima",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Peru",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 44,
    "text": "A summit was passed by Parliament impacting Geneva, Switzerland.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Parliament",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "Geneva",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Switzerland",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 45,
    "text": "Rachel Carson led trials of irrigation technique adoption in Punjab, India.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Rachel Carson",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "Punjab",
        "NORP"
      ],
      [
        "India",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 46,
    "text": "NBA announced a new tournament for 2022-2023.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "NBA",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "2022-2023",
        "DATE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 47,
    "text": "The expedition marked a turning point in Berlin, Germany's history.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Berlin",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Germany",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 48,
    "text": "M. S. Swaminathan led trials of yield improvement study in Punjab, India.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "M. S. Swaminathan",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "Punjab",
        "NORP"
      ],
      [
        "India",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 49,
    "text": "Pablo Picasso premiered a painting at Madrid, Spain.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Madrid",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Spain",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 50,
    "text": "The battle took place in Delhi, India and involved Roman Senate.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Delhi",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "India",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Roman Senate",
        "NORP"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 51,
    "text": "A famous exhibition by Leonardo da Vinci is housed in Metropolitan Opera in New York, USA.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Leonardo da Vinci",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "Metropolitan Opera",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "New York",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "USA",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 52,
    "text": "A policy announcement was passed by United Nations impacting Washington, USA.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "United Nations",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "Washington",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "USA",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 53,
    "text": "The uprising took place in Versailles, France and involved Allied Powers.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Versailles",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "France",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Allied Powers",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 54,
    "text": "The season opener in London, UK featured Lionel Messi and NBA.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "London",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "UK",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Lionel Messi",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "NBA",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 55,
    "text": "Records show uprising happened in Berlin, Germany around 1539-09-02.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Berlin",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Germany",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "1539-09-02",
        "DATE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 56,
    "text": "Kamala Harris met leaders from Parliament in Geneva, Switzerland to discuss summit.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Kamala Harris",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "Parliament",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "Geneva",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Switzerland",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 57,
    "text": "NASA announced a field research that impacts genetics.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "NASA",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 58,
    "text": "A study on particle discovery led by Rosalind Franklin was published on 1538-06-17.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Rosalind Franklin",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "1538-06-17",
        "DATE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 59,
    "text": "Siemens acquired Reliance Industries in a deal valued at $1.2B.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Siemens",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "Reliance Industries",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "1.2B.",
        "MONEY"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 60,
    "text": "A bill passage was passed by European Union impacting New Delhi, India.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "European Union",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "New Delhi",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "India",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 61,
    "text": "Researchers at CERN reported a field research in Cambridge, UK.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Cambridge",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "UK",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 62,
    "text": "Sydney Opera House announced restoration of the painting in New York, USA.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Sydney Opera House",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "New York",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "USA",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 63,
    "text": "Records show expedition happened in Constantinople, Turkey around 1757-05-31.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Constantinople",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Turkey",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "1757-05-31",
        "DATE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 64,
    "text": "The tournament in Madrid, Spain featured M.S. Dhoni and Wimbledon.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Madrid",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Spain",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "M.S. Dhoni",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "Wimbledon",
        "EVENT"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 65,
    "text": "Julius Caesar was a key figure in the Treaty signing.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Julius Caesar",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "Treaty",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 66,
    "text": "SpaceX released a robotics that improves 5G networks.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "SpaceX",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "5",
        "CARDINAL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 67,
    "text": "Records show battle happened in Constantinople, Turkey around 1549-02-10.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Constantinople",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Turkey",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "1549-02-10",
        "DATE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 68,
    "text": "Max Planck Institute announced a particle discovery that impacts climatology.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Max Planck Institute",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 69,
    "text": "Records show coronation happened in Rome, Italy around 1988-08-07.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Rome",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Italy",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "1988-08-07",
        "DATE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 70,
    "text": "Farmers in Lima, Peru adopted irrigation technique adoption developed by ICAR.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Lima",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Peru",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "ICAR",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 71,
    "text": "The season opener in London, UK featured Serena Williams and FC Barcelona.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "London",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "UK",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Serena Williams",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "FC Barcelona",
        "PERSON"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 72,
    "text": "Norman Borlaug led trials of yield improvement study in Nairobi, Kenya.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Norman Borlaug",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "Nairobi",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Kenya",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 73,
    "text": "Records show coronation happened in Constantinople, Turkey around 1821-08-26.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Constantinople",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Turkey",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "1821-08-26",
        "DATE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 74,
    "text": "Beyoncé exhibited a new exhibition at Tate Modern.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Beyoncé",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "Tate Modern",
        "FAC"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 75,
    "text": "A breakthrough in 5G networks was reported by OpenAI.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "5",
        "CARDINAL"
      ],
      [
        "OpenAI",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 76,
    "text": "Wimbledon announced a new season opener for 2024-2025.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Wimbledon",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "2024-2025",
        "DATE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 77,
    "text": "Beyoncé premiered a exhibition at Vienna, Austria.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Beyoncé",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "Vienna",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Austria",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 78,
    "text": "Indra Nooyi became CEO of Siemens following the merger.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Indra Nooyi",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "Siemens",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 79,
    "text": "The season opener in Madrid, Spain featured Lionel Messi and NBA.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Madrid",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Spain",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Lionel Messi",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "NBA",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 80,
    "text": "Norman Borlaug led trials of irrigation technique adoption in Iowa, USA.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Norman Borlaug",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "Iowa",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "USA",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 81,
    "text": "Sydney Opera House announced restoration of the opera in Madrid, Spain.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Sydney Opera House",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "Madrid",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Spain",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 82,
    "text": "A breakthrough in AI-driven sensors was reported by Apple.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "AI",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Apple",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 83,
    "text": "Barack Obama met leaders from Congress in Washington, USA to discuss policy announcement.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Barack Obama",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "Congress",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "Washington",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "USA",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 84,
    "text": "Mahatma Gandhi was a key figure in the Treaty signing.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Mahatma Gandhi",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "Treaty",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 85,
    "text": "A study by Norman Borlaug showed benefits of pest control trial for soybeans.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Norman Borlaug",
        "PERSON"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 86,
    "text": "Samsung acquired Reliance Industries in a deal valued at $15M.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Samsung",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "Reliance Industries",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "15M.",
        "MONEY"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 87,
    "text": "A study by M. S. Swaminathan showed benefits of yield improvement study for maize.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "M. S. Swaminathan",
        "PERSON"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 88,
    "text": "Wangari Maathai led trials of pest control trial in Iowa, USA.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Wangari Maathai",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "Iowa",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "USA",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 89,
    "text": "Researchers at Harvard University reported a field research in Cape Town, South Africa.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Harvard University",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "Cape Town",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "South Africa",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 90,
    "text": "merger led to restructuring at Goldman Sachs.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Goldman Sachs",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 91,
    "text": "A breakthrough in robotics was reported by SpaceX.",
    "entities": []
  },
  {
    "id": 92,
    "text": "Wimbledon announced a new final match for 2022-2023.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Wimbledon",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "2022-2023",
        "DATE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 93,
    "text": "The season opener in Madrid, Spain featured Cristiano Ronaldo and Wimbledon.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Madrid",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Spain",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Cristiano Ronaldo",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "Wimbledon",
        "EVENT"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 94,
    "text": "Albert Einstein published findings on particle discovery at NASA.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Albert Einstein",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "NASA",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 95,
    "text": "Researchers at NASA reported a field research in Cambridge, UK.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "NASA",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "Cambridge",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "UK",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 96,
    "text": "Kamala Harris announced policy changes regarding climate at Washington, USA.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Kamala Harris",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "Washington",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "USA",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 97,
    "text": "A study by Wangari Maathai showed benefits of yield improvement study for maize.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Wangari Maathai",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 98,
    "text": "Google released a 5G networks that improves robotics.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Google",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "5",
        "CARDINAL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 99,
    "text": "A study by Rachel Carson showed benefits of irrigation technique adoption for wheat.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Rachel Carson",
        "PERSON"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 100,
    "text": "Ada Lovelace led the launch of a quantum computing in London, UK.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Ada Lovelace",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "London",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "UK",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 101,
    "text": "Siemens opened a new office in Mumbai, India to expand cloud services.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Siemens",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "Mumbai",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "India",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 102,
    "text": "Marissa Mayer led the launch of a robotics in Shenzhen, China.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Marissa Mayer",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "Shenzhen",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "China",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 103,
    "text": "Grace Hopper announced a new 5G networks at Apple.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Grace Hopper",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "5",
        "CARDINAL"
      ],
      [
        "Apple",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 104,
    "text": "Wimbledon announced a new tournament for 2022-2023.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Wimbledon",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "2022-2023",
        "DATE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 105,
    "text": "Indra Nooyi became CEO of Siemens following the IPO.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Indra Nooyi",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "Siemens",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "IPO",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 106,
    "text": "A summit was passed by Parliament impacting Geneva, Switzerland.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Parliament",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "Geneva",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Switzerland",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 107,
    "text": "Tim Cook became CEO of Samsung following the IPO.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Tim Cook",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "Samsung",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "IPO",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 108,
    "text": "Farmers in Nairobi, Kenya adopted yield improvement study developed by AgriTech Ltd.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Nairobi",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Kenya",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "AgriTech Ltd.",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 109,
    "text": "Mahatma Gandhi was a key figure in the battle.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Mahatma Gandhi",
        "PERSON"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 110,
    "text": "Records show uprising happened in Constantinople, Turkey around 1537-02-18.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Constantinople",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Turkey",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "1537-02-18",
        "DATE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 111,
    "text": "CERN announced a particle discovery that impacts genetics.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "CERN",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 112,
    "text": "Researchers at NASA reported a particle discovery in Cape Town, South Africa.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "NASA",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "Cape Town",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "South Africa",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 113,
    "text": "Jane Goodall published findings on field research at CERN.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Jane Goodall",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "CERN",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 114,
    "text": "ICAR introduced a irrigation technique adoption to improve yields in Nairobi, Kenya.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Nairobi",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Kenya",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 115,
    "text": "Reliance Industries acquired Reliance Industries in a deal valued at $450M.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Reliance Industries",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "Reliance Industries",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "450M.",
        "MONEY"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 116,
    "text": "Sundar Pichai became CEO of Reliance Industries following the merger.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Sundar Pichai",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "Reliance Industries",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 117,
    "text": "A policy announcement was passed by European Union impacting Washington, USA.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "European Union",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "Washington",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "USA",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 118,
    "text": "ICAR introduced a irrigation technique adoption to improve yields in Nairobi, Kenya.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Nairobi",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Kenya",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 119,
    "text": "International Rice Research Institute introduced a irrigation technique adoption to improve yields in Lima, Peru.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "International Rice Research Institute",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "Lima",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Peru",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 120,
    "text": "A study by Wangari Maathai showed benefits of pest control trial for soybeans.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Wangari Maathai",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 121,
    "text": "Satya Nadella led the launch of a AI-driven sensors in Shenzhen, China.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Satya Nadella",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "AI",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Shenzhen",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "China",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 122,
    "text": "NBA announced a new season opener for 2022-2023.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "NBA",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "2022-2023",
        "DATE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 123,
    "text": "Marissa Mayer led the launch of a quantum computing in Bengaluru, India.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Marissa Mayer",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "Bengaluru",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "India",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 124,
    "text": "Tim Berners-Lee announced a new 5G networks at Google.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Tim Berners-Lee",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "5",
        "CARDINAL"
      ],
      [
        "Google",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 125,
    "text": "Rosalind Franklin published findings on climate study at Max Planck Institute.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Franklin",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "Max Planck Institute",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 126,
    "text": "A study on climate study led by Rosalind Franklin was published on 1980-12-14.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Rosalind Franklin",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "1980-12-14",
        "DATE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 127,
    "text": "A famous painting by Ludwig van Beethoven is housed in Metropolitan Opera in Paris, France.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Ludwig van Beethoven",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "Metropolitan Opera",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "Paris",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "France",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 128,
    "text": "Rachel Carson led trials of irrigation technique adoption in Lima, Peru.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Rachel Carson",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "Lima",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Peru",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 129,
    "text": "Farmers in Punjab, India adopted yield improvement study developed by International Rice Research Institute.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Punjab",
        "NORP"
      ],
      [
        "India",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "International Rice Research Institute",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 130,
    "text": "Kamala Harris met leaders from European Union in Washington, USA to discuss summit.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Kamala Harris",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "European Union",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "Washington",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "USA",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 131,
    "text": "Grace Hopper announced a new AI-driven sensors at Intel.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Grace Hopper",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "AI",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Intel",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 132,
    "text": "Pablo Picasso premiered a symphony at Paris, France.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Paris",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "France",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 133,
    "text": "A study on gene sequencing led by Jane Goodall was published on 1749-01-26.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Jane Goodall",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "1749-01-26",
        "DATE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 134,
    "text": "Indra Nooyi became CEO of Samsung following the merger.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Indra Nooyi",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "Samsung",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 135,
    "text": "Sundar Pichai led the launch of a quantum computing in Stockholm, Sweden.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Sundar Pichai",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "Stockholm",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Sweden",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 136,
    "text": "Angela Merkel met leaders from European Union in Washington, USA to discuss policy announcement.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Angela Merkel",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "European Union",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "Washington",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "USA",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 137,
    "text": "Marissa Mayer led the launch of a robotics in Shenzhen, China.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Marissa Mayer",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "Shenzhen",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "China",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 138,
    "text": "FC Barcelona announced a new final match for 2022-2023.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Barcelona",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "2022-2023",
        "DATE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 139,
    "text": "Farmers in Nairobi, Kenya adopted yield improvement study developed by ICAR.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Nairobi",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Kenya",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "ICAR",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 140,
    "text": "Farmers in Nairobi, Kenya adopted yield improvement study developed by CIMMYT.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Nairobi",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Kenya",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "CIMMYT",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 141,
    "text": "Mary Barra became CEO of Samsung following the acquisition.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Mary Barra",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "Samsung",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 142,
    "text": "Barack Obama announced policy changes regarding climate at Geneva, Switzerland.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Barack Obama",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "Geneva",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Switzerland",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 143,
    "text": "Marissa Mayer led the launch of a AI-driven sensors in London, UK.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Marissa Mayer",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "AI",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "London",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "UK",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 144,
    "text": "Marie Curie published findings on particle discovery at CERN.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Marie Curie",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "CERN",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 145,
    "text": "A bill passage was passed by Parliament impacting Washington, USA.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Parliament",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "Washington",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "USA",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 146,
    "text": "Harvard University announced a gene sequencing that impacts physics.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Harvard University",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 147,
    "text": "The Treaty signing took place in Berlin, Germany and involved Mughal Empire.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Treaty",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "Berlin",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Germany",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Mughal Empire",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 148,
    "text": "Wimbledon announced a new season opener for 2022-2023.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Wimbledon",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "2022-2023",
        "DATE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 149,
    "text": "Reliance Industries acquired Goldman Sachs in a deal valued at $450M.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Reliance Industries",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "Goldman Sachs",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "450M.",
        "MONEY"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 150,
    "text": "Reliance Industries opened a new office in Mumbai, India to expand cloud services.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Reliance Industries",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "Mumbai",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "India",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 151,
    "text": "Pablo Picasso premiered a installation at Paris, France.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Paris",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "France",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 152,
    "text": "Researchers at Harvard University reported a climate study in Cape Town, South Africa.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Harvard University",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "Cape Town",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "South Africa",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 153,
    "text": "Jane Goodall published findings on field research at NASA.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Jane Goodall",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "NASA",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 154,
    "text": "The battle marked a turning point in Berlin, Germany's history.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Berlin",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Germany",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 155,
    "text": "SpaceX released a edge computing that improves quantum computing.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "SpaceX",
        "PERSON"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 156,
    "text": "Nelson Mandela was a key figure in the expedition.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Nelson Mandela",
        "PERSON"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 157,
    "text": "The tournament in Madrid, Spain featured M.S. Dhoni and Wimbledon.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Madrid",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Spain",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "M.S. Dhoni",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "Wimbledon",
        "EVENT"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 158,
    "text": "Grace Hopper announced a new 5G networks at Apple.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Grace Hopper",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "5",
        "CARDINAL"
      ],
      [
        "Apple",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 159,
    "text": "The Treaty signing marked a turning point in Delhi, India's history.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Treaty",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "Delhi",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "India",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 160,
    "text": "Narendra Modi announced policy changes regarding climate at Geneva, Switzerland.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Narendra Modi",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "Geneva",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Switzerland",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 161,
    "text": "Siemens acquired Reliance Industries in a deal valued at $1.2B.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Siemens",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "Reliance Industries",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "1.2B.",
        "MONEY"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 162,
    "text": "A breakthrough in 5G networks was reported by SpaceX.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "5",
        "CARDINAL"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 163,
    "text": "Farmers in Punjab, India adopted yield improvement study developed by ICAR.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Punjab",
        "NORP"
      ],
      [
        "India",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "ICAR",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 164,
    "text": "CERN announced a gene sequencing that impacts genetics.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "CERN",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 165,
    "text": "A study on field research led by Marie Curie was published on 1882-10-03.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Marie Curie",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "1882-10-03",
        "DATE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 166,
    "text": "Angela Merkel announced policy changes regarding healthcare at Geneva, Switzerland.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Angela Merkel",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "Geneva",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Switzerland",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 167,
    "text": "Marissa Mayer led the launch of a quantum computing in Silicon Valley, USA.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Marissa Mayer",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "Silicon Valley",
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        "USA",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 168,
    "text": "A summit was passed by Parliament impacting New Delhi, India.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Parliament",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "New Delhi",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "India",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 169,
    "text": "Narendra Modi announced policy changes regarding healthcare at New Delhi, India.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Narendra Modi",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "New Delhi",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "India",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 170,
    "text": "The coronation took place in Berlin, Germany and involved Ottoman Empire.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Berlin",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Germany",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Ottoman Empire",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 171,
    "text": "AgriTech Ltd introduced a irrigation technique adoption to improve yields in Punjab, India.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "AgriTech Ltd",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "Punjab",
        "NORP"
      ],
      [
        "India",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 172,
    "text": "NASA announced a field research that impacts biology.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "NASA",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 173,
    "text": "The coronation marked a turning point in Berlin, Germany's history.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Berlin",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Germany",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 174,
    "text": "The final match in London, UK featured M.S. Dhoni and NBA.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "London",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "UK",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "M.S. Dhoni",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "NBA",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 175,
    "text": "A bill passage was passed by United Nations impacting Washington, USA.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "United Nations",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "Washington",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "USA",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 176,
    "text": "Tesla acquired Tesla in a deal valued at $15M.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Tesla",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "Tesla",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "15M.",
        "MONEY"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 177,
    "text": "The coronation marked a turning point in Constantinople, Turkey's history.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Constantinople",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Turkey",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 178,
    "text": "Marissa Mayer announced a new robotics at Apple.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Marissa Mayer",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "Apple",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 179,
    "text": "Goldman Sachs opened a new office in New York, USA to expand consumer electronics.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Goldman Sachs",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "New York",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "USA",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 180,
    "text": "Farmers in Nairobi, Kenya adopted irrigation technique adoption developed by AgriTech Ltd.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Nairobi",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Kenya",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "AgriTech Ltd.",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 181,
    "text": "The Treaty signing marked a turning point in Constantinople, Turkey's history.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Treaty",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "Constantinople",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Turkey",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 182,
    "text": "Serena Williams led Wimbledon to victory at the tournament in Madrid, Spain.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Serena Williams",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "Wimbledon",
        "EVENT"
      ],
      [
        "Madrid",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Spain",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 183,
    "text": "Jamie Dimon became CEO of Tesla following the acquisition.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Jamie Dimon",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "Tesla",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 184,
    "text": "AgriTech Ltd introduced a irrigation technique adoption to improve yields in Lima, Peru.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "AgriTech Ltd",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "Lima",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Peru",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 185,
    "text": "Records show coronation happened in Delhi, India around 1841-04-20.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Delhi",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "India",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "1841-04-20",
        "DATE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 186,
    "text": "Rachel Carson led trials of pest control trial in Iowa, USA.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Rachel Carson",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "Iowa",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "USA",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 187,
    "text": "A summit was passed by European Union impacting Geneva, Switzerland.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "European Union",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "Geneva",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Switzerland",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 188,
    "text": "Wimbledon announced a new final match for 2023-2024.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Wimbledon",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "2023-2024",
        "DATE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 189,
    "text": "The final match in Madrid, Spain featured Cristiano Ronaldo and Wimbledon.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Madrid",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Spain",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Cristiano Ronaldo",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "Wimbledon",
        "EVENT"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 190,
    "text": "A famous opera by Pablo Picasso is housed in Sydney Opera House in Madrid, Spain.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Pablo Picasso",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "Sydney Opera House",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "Madrid",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Spain",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 191,
    "text": "The season opener in London, UK featured M.S. Dhoni and FC Barcelona.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "London",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "UK",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "M.S. Dhoni",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "FC Barcelona",
        "PERSON"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 192,
    "text": "The final match in Madrid, Spain featured M.S. Dhoni and NBA.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Madrid",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Spain",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "M.S. Dhoni",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "NBA",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 193,
    "text": "CERN announced a climate study that impacts genetics.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "CERN",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 194,
    "text": "Isaac Newton published findings on field research at CERN.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Isaac Newton",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "CERN",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 195,
    "text": "Max Planck Institute announced a field research that impacts climatology.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Max Planck Institute",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 196,
    "text": "A breakthrough in edge computing was reported by OpenAI.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "OpenAI",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 197,
    "text": "A study by George Washington Carver showed benefits of yield improvement study for soybeans.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "George Washington Carver",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 198,
    "text": "Indra Nooyi became CEO of Siemens following the restructuring.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Indra Nooyi",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "Siemens",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 199,
    "text": "Grace Hopper led the launch of a 5G networks in Stockholm, Sweden.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Grace Hopper",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "5",
        "CARDINAL"
      ],
      [
        "Stockholm",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Sweden",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 200,
    "text": "Siemens acquired Samsung in a deal valued at $1.2B.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Siemens",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "Samsung",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "1.2B.",
        "MONEY"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 201,
    "text": "A bill passage was passed by Parliament impacting Washington, USA.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Parliament",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "Washington",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "USA",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 202,
    "text": "Researchers at Harvard University reported a field research in Cambridge, UK.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Harvard University",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "Cambridge",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "UK",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 203,
    "text": "Angela Merkel announced policy changes regarding climate at Washington, USA.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Angela Merkel",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "Washington",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "USA",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 204,
    "text": "NBA announced a new season opener for 2024-2025.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "NBA",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "2024-2025",
        "DATE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 205,
    "text": "NBA announced a new season opener for 2023-2024.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "NBA",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "2023-2024",
        "DATE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 206,
    "text": "Barack Obama met leaders from United Nations in New Delhi, India to discuss policy announcement.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Barack Obama",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "United Nations",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "New Delhi",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "India",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 207,
    "text": "A policy announcement was passed by Parliament impacting Geneva, Switzerland.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Parliament",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "Geneva",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Switzerland",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 208,
    "text": "Researchers at CERN reported a climate study in Cape Town, South Africa.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Cape Town",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "South Africa",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 209,
    "text": "Angela Merkel announced policy changes regarding education at Geneva, Switzerland.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Angela Merkel",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "Geneva",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Switzerland",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 210,
    "text": "The expedition marked a turning point in Delhi, India's history.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Delhi",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "India",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 211,
    "text": "Goldman Sachs acquired Siemens in a deal valued at $1.2B.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Goldman Sachs",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "Siemens",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "1.2B.",
        "MONEY"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 212,
    "text": "Records show uprising happened in Delhi, India around 1726-07-15.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Delhi",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "India",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "1726-07-15",
        "DATE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 213,
    "text": "merger led to restructuring at Tesla.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Tesla",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 214,
    "text": "Narendra Modi announced policy changes regarding climate at New Delhi, India.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Narendra Modi",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "New Delhi",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "India",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 215,
    "text": "Samsung acquired Tesla in a deal valued at $450M.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Samsung",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "Tesla",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "450M.",
        "MONEY"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 216,
    "text": "Wimbledon announced a new season opener for 2022-2023.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Wimbledon",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "2022-2023",
        "DATE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 217,
    "text": "A bill passage was passed by Parliament impacting Washington, USA.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Parliament",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "Washington",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "USA",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 218,
    "text": "restructuring led to restructuring at Goldman Sachs.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Goldman Sachs",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 219,
    "text": "A breakthrough in 5G networks was reported by Intel.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "5",
        "CARDINAL"
      ],
      [
        "Intel",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 220,
    "text": "acquisition led to restructuring at Siemens.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Siemens",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 221,
    "text": "Elon Musk announced a new edge computing at IBM.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Elon Musk",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "IBM",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 222,
    "text": "A study by Wangari Maathai showed benefits of yield improvement study for maize.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Wangari Maathai",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 223,
    "text": "restructuring led to restructuring at Samsung.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Samsung",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 224,
    "text": "The coronation took place in Rome, Italy and involved British Empire.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Rome",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Italy",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "British Empire",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 225,
    "text": "The expedition marked a turning point in Berlin, Germany's history.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Berlin",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Germany",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 226,
    "text": "Samsung opened a new office in Frankfurt, Germany to expand financial services.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Samsung",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "Frankfurt",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Germany",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 227,
    "text": "Barack Obama met leaders from Parliament in Geneva, Switzerland to discuss bill passage.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Barack Obama",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "Parliament",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "Geneva",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Switzerland",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 228,
    "text": "A study by Norman Borlaug showed benefits of yield improvement study for maize.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Norman Borlaug",
        "PERSON"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 229,
    "text": "FAO introduced a pest control trial to improve yields in Nairobi, Kenya.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "FAO",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "Nairobi",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Kenya",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 230,
    "text": "Jamie Dimon became CEO of Tesla following the IPO.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Jamie Dimon",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "Tesla",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "IPO",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 231,
    "text": "Researchers at Harvard University reported a field research in Cape Town, South Africa.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Harvard University",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "Cape Town",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "South Africa",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 232,
    "text": "Kamala Harris announced policy changes regarding healthcare at New Delhi, India.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Kamala Harris",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "New Delhi",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "India",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 233,
    "text": "A summit was passed by United Nations impacting Washington, USA.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "United Nations",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "Washington",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "USA",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 234,
    "text": "A study by M. S. Swaminathan showed benefits of irrigation technique adoption for soybeans.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "M. S. Swaminathan",
        "PERSON"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 235,
    "text": "FAO introduced a yield improvement study to improve yields in Iowa, USA.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "FAO",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "Iowa",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "USA",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 236,
    "text": "NBA announced a new final match for 2024-2025.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "NBA",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "2024-2025",
        "DATE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 237,
    "text": "Narendra Modi announced policy changes regarding trade at Washington, USA.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Narendra Modi",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "Washington",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "USA",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 238,
    "text": "Sundar Pichai became CEO of Reliance Industries following the acquisition.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Sundar Pichai",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "Reliance Industries",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 239,
    "text": "The season opener in Madrid, Spain featured Serena Williams and NBA.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Madrid",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Spain",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Serena Williams",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "NBA",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 240,
    "text": "Tesla acquired Tesla in a deal valued at $450M.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Tesla",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "Tesla",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "450M.",
        "MONEY"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 241,
    "text": "Samsung opened a new office in Mumbai, India to expand manufacturing.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Samsung",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "Mumbai",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "India",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 242,
    "text": "A study by Norman Borlaug showed benefits of irrigation technique adoption for soybeans.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Norman Borlaug",
        "PERSON"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 243,
    "text": "A breakthrough in AI-driven sensors was reported by Apple.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "AI",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Apple",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 244,
    "text": "George Washington Carver led trials of irrigation technique adoption in Nairobi, Kenya.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "George Washington Carver",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "Nairobi",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Kenya",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 245,
    "text": "NASA announced a climate study that impacts biology.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "NASA",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 246,
    "text": "Lionel Messi led NBA to victory at the final match in London, UK.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Lionel Messi",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "NBA",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "London",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "UK",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 247,
    "text": "Researchers at Max Planck Institute reported a particle discovery in Geneva, Switzerland.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Max Planck Institute",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "Geneva",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Switzerland",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 248,
    "text": "Narendra Modi announced policy changes regarding education at Washington, USA.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Narendra Modi",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "Washington",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "USA",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 249,
    "text": "acquisition led to restructuring at Tesla.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Tesla",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 250,
    "text": "Samsung opened a new office in Frankfurt, Germany to expand cloud services.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Samsung",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "Frankfurt",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Germany",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 251,
    "text": "A study on climate study led by Isaac Newton was published on 1683-02-14.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Isaac Newton",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "1683-02-14",
        "DATE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 252,
    "text": "The tournament in Melbourne, Australia featured M.S. Dhoni and FC Barcelona.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Melbourne",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Australia",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "M.S. Dhoni",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "FC Barcelona",
        "PERSON"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 253,
    "text": "M.S. Dhoni led Team India to victory at the season opener in Madrid, Spain.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "M.S. Dhoni",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "Madrid",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Spain",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 254,
    "text": "Marissa Mayer led the launch of a AI-driven sensors in Shenzhen, China.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Marissa Mayer",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "AI",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Shenzhen",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "China",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 255,
    "text": "Rosalind Franklin published findings on particle discovery at Harvard University.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Harvard University",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 256,
    "text": "restructuring led to restructuring at Siemens.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Siemens",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 257,
    "text": "A famous installation by Ludwig van Beethoven is housed in Tate Modern in New York, USA.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Ludwig van Beethoven",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "Tate Modern",
        "FAC"
      ],
      [
        "New York",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "USA",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 258,
    "text": "The final match in London, UK featured M.S. Dhoni and Team India.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "London",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "UK",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "M.S. Dhoni",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "Team India",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 259,
    "text": "Team India announced a new season opener for 2022-2023.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Team India",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "2022-2023",
        "DATE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 260,
    "text": "Researchers at Harvard University reported a field research in Cambridge, UK.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Harvard University",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "Cambridge",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "UK",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 261,
    "text": "Records show uprising happened in Versailles, France around 1717-08-11.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Versailles",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "France",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "1717-08-11",
        "DATE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 262,
    "text": "Elon Musk led the launch of a quantum computing in London, UK.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Elon Musk",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "London",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "UK",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 263,
    "text": "Researchers at NASA reported a particle discovery in Cambridge, UK.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "NASA",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "Cambridge",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "UK",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 264,
    "text": "Sundar Pichai led the launch of a 5G networks in Silicon Valley, USA.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Sundar Pichai",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "5",
        "CARDINAL"
      ],
      [
        "Silicon Valley",
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        "USA",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 265,
    "text": "Sundar Pichai became CEO of Reliance Industries following the IPO.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Sundar Pichai",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "Reliance Industries",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "IPO",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 266,
    "text": "The battle marked a turning point in Versailles, France's history.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Versailles",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "France",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 267,
    "text": "Queen Elizabeth I was a key figure in the expedition.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Elizabeth",
        "PERSON"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 268,
    "text": "A policy announcement was passed by Parliament impacting Washington, USA.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Parliament",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "Washington",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "USA",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 269,
    "text": "A breakthrough in quantum computing was reported by IBM.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "IBM",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 270,
    "text": "Harvard University announced a climate study that impacts biology.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Harvard University",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 271,
    "text": "acquisition led to restructuring at Samsung.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Samsung",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 272,
    "text": "Sundar Pichai led the launch of a robotics in Shenzhen, China.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Sundar Pichai",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "Shenzhen",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "China",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 273,
    "text": "Records show battle happened in Delhi, India around 1750-10-07.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Delhi",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "India",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "1750-10-07",
        "DATE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 274,
    "text": "Researchers at Harvard University reported a gene sequencing in Cape Town, South Africa.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Harvard University",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "Cape Town",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "South Africa",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 275,
    "text": "Researchers at Harvard University reported a field research in Cape Town, South Africa.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Harvard University",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "Cape Town",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "South Africa",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 276,
    "text": "Records show Treaty signing happened in Constantinople, Turkey around 1622-01-17.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Constantinople",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Turkey",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "1622-01-17",
        "DATE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 277,
    "text": "Siemens opened a new office in Frankfurt, Germany to expand consumer electronics.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Siemens",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "Frankfurt",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Germany",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 278,
    "text": "Barack Obama met leaders from Congress in Washington, USA to discuss bill passage.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Barack Obama",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "Congress",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "Washington",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "USA",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 279,
    "text": "Mary Barra became CEO of Siemens following the merger.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Mary Barra",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "Siemens",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 280,
    "text": "Team India announced a new season opener for 2023-2024.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Team India",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "2023-2024",
        "DATE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 281,
    "text": "Ludwig van Beethoven exhibited a new exhibition at Sydney Opera House.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Ludwig van Beethoven",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "Sydney Opera House",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 282,
    "text": "Barack Obama announced policy changes regarding climate at Washington, USA.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Barack Obama",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "Washington",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "USA",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 283,
    "text": "A famous exhibition by Vincent van Gogh is housed in Louvre Museum in Vienna, Austria.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Vincent van Gogh",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "Louvre Museum",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "Vienna",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Austria",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 284,
    "text": "Mary Barra became CEO of Reliance Industries following the acquisition.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Mary Barra",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "Reliance Industries",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 285,
    "text": "Researchers at NASA reported a particle discovery in Geneva, Switzerland.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "NASA",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "Geneva",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Switzerland",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 286,
    "text": "A study by Norman Borlaug showed benefits of yield improvement study for rice.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Norman Borlaug",
        "PERSON"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 287,
    "text": "merger led to restructuring at Goldman Sachs.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Goldman Sachs",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 288,
    "text": "Researchers at Harvard University reported a particle discovery in Geneva, Switzerland.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Harvard University",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "Geneva",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Switzerland",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 289,
    "text": "Tesla opened a new office in New York, USA to expand manufacturing.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Tesla",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "New York",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "USA",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 290,
    "text": "Pablo Picasso exhibited a new painting at Tate Modern.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Tate Modern",
        "FAC"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 291,
    "text": "Reliance Industries acquired Reliance Industries in a deal valued at $1.2B.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Reliance Industries",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "Reliance Industries",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "1.2B.",
        "MONEY"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 292,
    "text": "Pablo Picasso exhibited a new painting at Metropolitan Opera.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Metropolitan Opera",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 293,
    "text": "Ludwig van Beethoven premiered a exhibition at Madrid, Spain.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Ludwig van Beethoven",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "Madrid",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Spain",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 294,
    "text": "The expedition marked a turning point in Berlin, Germany's history.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Berlin",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Germany",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 295,
    "text": "Marissa Mayer announced a new quantum computing at Intel.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Marissa Mayer",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "Intel",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 296,
    "text": "Jamie Dimon became CEO of Siemens following the acquisition.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Jamie Dimon",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "Siemens",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 297,
    "text": "Max Planck Institute announced a climate study that impacts biology.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Max Planck Institute",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 298,
    "text": "The uprising marked a turning point in Delhi, India's history.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Delhi",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "India",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 299,
    "text": "Louvre Museum announced restoration of the painting in Paris, France.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Louvre Museum",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "Paris",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "France",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 300,
    "text": "Isaac Newton published findings on field research at NASA.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Isaac Newton",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "NASA",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 301,
    "text": "Lionel Messi led Wimbledon to victory at the final match in London, UK.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Lionel Messi",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "Wimbledon",
        "EVENT"
      ],
      [
        "London",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "UK",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 302,
    "text": "Wimbledon announced a new season opener for 2023-2024.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Wimbledon",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "2023-2024",
        "DATE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 303,
    "text": "Records show coronation happened in Versailles, France around 1515-11-09.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Versailles",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "France",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "1515-11-09",
        "DATE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 304,
    "text": "IBM released a AI-driven sensors that improves AI-driven sensors.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "IBM",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "AI",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "AI",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 305,
    "text": "The coronation took place in Constantinople, Turkey and involved British Empire.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Constantinople",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Turkey",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "British Empire",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 306,
    "text": "Farmers in Nairobi, Kenya adopted irrigation technique adoption developed by International Rice Research Institute.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Nairobi",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Kenya",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "International Rice Research Institute",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 307,
    "text": "Louvre Museum announced restoration of the symphony in Paris, France.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Louvre Museum",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "Paris",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "France",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 308,
    "text": "Tim Berners-Lee led the launch of a robotics in Bengaluru, India.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Tim Berners-Lee",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "Bengaluru",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "India",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 309,
    "text": "Serena Williams led Wimbledon to victory at the final match in Melbourne, Australia.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Serena Williams",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "Wimbledon",
        "EVENT"
      ],
      [
        "Melbourne",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Australia",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 310,
    "text": "A study on particle discovery led by Marie Curie was published on 1912-08-20.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Marie Curie",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "1912-08-20",
        "DATE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 311,
    "text": "Albert Einstein published findings on particle discovery at CERN.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Albert Einstein",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "CERN",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 312,
    "text": "M. S. Swaminathan led trials of yield improvement study in Iowa, USA.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "M. S. Swaminathan",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "Iowa",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "USA",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 313,
    "text": "IPO led to restructuring at Samsung.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "IPO",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "Samsung",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 314,
    "text": "A study on climate study led by Isaac Newton was published on 1537-01-31.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Isaac Newton",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "1537-01-31",
        "DATE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 315,
    "text": "Narendra Modi met leaders from Parliament in Washington, USA to discuss policy announcement.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Narendra Modi",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "Parliament",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "Washington",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "USA",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 316,
    "text": "Farmers in Nairobi, Kenya adopted pest control trial developed by ICAR.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Nairobi",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Kenya",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "ICAR",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 317,
    "text": "Grace Hopper led the launch of a robotics in Silicon Valley, USA.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Grace Hopper",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "Silicon Valley",
        "LOC"
      ],
      [
        "USA",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 318,
    "text": "Leonardo da Vinci exhibited a new exhibition at Royal Academy.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Leonardo da Vinci",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "Royal Academy",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 319,
    "text": "Albert Einstein published findings on particle discovery at CERN.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Albert Einstein",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "CERN",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 320,
    "text": "Marie Curie published findings on field research at Harvard University.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Marie Curie",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "Harvard University",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 321,
    "text": "ICAR introduced a pest control trial to improve yields in Nairobi, Kenya.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Nairobi",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Kenya",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 322,
    "text": "Mahatma Gandhi was a key figure in the coronation.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Mahatma Gandhi",
        "PERSON"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 323,
    "text": "The battle marked a turning point in Berlin, Germany's history.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Berlin",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Germany",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 324,
    "text": "Records show uprising happened in Delhi, India around 1577-11-19.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Delhi",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "India",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "1577-11-19",
        "DATE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 325,
    "text": "Cristiano Ronaldo led NBA to victory at the final match in Melbourne, Australia.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Cristiano Ronaldo",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "NBA",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "Melbourne",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Australia",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 326,
    "text": "The tournament in Madrid, Spain featured Serena Williams and NBA.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Madrid",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Spain",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Serena Williams",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "NBA",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 327,
    "text": "Royal Academy announced restoration of the symphony in Vienna, Austria.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Royal Academy",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "Vienna",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Austria",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 328,
    "text": "Reliance Industries opened a new office in Seoul, South Korea to expand financial services.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Reliance Industries",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "Seoul",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "South Korea",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 329,
    "text": "Elon Musk announced a new robotics at Intel.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Elon Musk",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "Intel",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 330,
    "text": "Cristiano Ronaldo led NBA to victory at the final match in London, UK.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Cristiano Ronaldo",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "NBA",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "London",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "UK",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 331,
    "text": "The tournament in Madrid, Spain featured Cristiano Ronaldo and NBA.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Madrid",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Spain",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Cristiano Ronaldo",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "NBA",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 332,
    "text": "Ada Lovelace led the launch of a 5G networks in Bengaluru, India.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Ada Lovelace",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "5",
        "CARDINAL"
      ],
      [
        "Bengaluru",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "India",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 333,
    "text": "A bill passage was passed by Congress impacting Geneva, Switzerland.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Congress",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "Geneva",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Switzerland",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 334,
    "text": "A summit was passed by United Nations impacting Washington, USA.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "United Nations",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "Washington",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "USA",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 335,
    "text": "Rachel Carson led trials of irrigation technique adoption in Punjab, India.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Rachel Carson",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "Punjab",
        "NORP"
      ],
      [
        "India",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 336,
    "text": "A famous exhibition by Frida Kahlo is housed in Metropolitan Opera in New York, USA.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Frida Kahlo",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "Metropolitan Opera",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "New York",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "USA",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 337,
    "text": "A breakthrough in edge computing was reported by OpenAI.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "OpenAI",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 338,
    "text": "A study by M. S. Swaminathan showed benefits of yield improvement study for wheat.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "M. S. Swaminathan",
        "PERSON"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 339,
    "text": "Jamie Dimon became CEO of Reliance Industries following the IPO.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Jamie Dimon",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "Reliance Industries",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "IPO",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 340,
    "text": "A breakthrough in robotics was reported by SpaceX.",
    "entities": []
  },
  {
    "id": 341,
    "text": "Narendra Modi announced policy changes regarding healthcare at New Delhi, India.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Narendra Modi",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "New Delhi",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "India",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 342,
    "text": "A bill passage was passed by Parliament impacting New Delhi, India.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Parliament",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "New Delhi",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "India",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 343,
    "text": "A study by Norman Borlaug showed benefits of yield improvement study for soybeans.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Norman Borlaug",
        "PERSON"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 344,
    "text": "The tournament in Madrid, Spain featured Serena Williams and Team India.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Madrid",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Spain",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Serena Williams",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "Team India",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 345,
    "text": "Leonardo da Vinci exhibited a new painting at Sydney Opera House.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Leonardo da Vinci",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "Sydney Opera House",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 346,
    "text": "A study by Norman Borlaug showed benefits of irrigation technique adoption for maize.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Norman Borlaug",
        "PERSON"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 347,
    "text": "restructuring led to restructuring at Samsung.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Samsung",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 348,
    "text": "A breakthrough in robotics was reported by Microsoft.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Microsoft",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 349,
    "text": "Siemens opened a new office in Seoul, South Korea to expand financial services.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Siemens",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "Seoul",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "South Korea",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 350,
    "text": "A study by Norman Borlaug showed benefits of irrigation technique adoption for wheat.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Norman Borlaug",
        "PERSON"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 351,
    "text": "Team India announced a new tournament for 2022-2023.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Team India",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "2022-2023",
        "DATE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 352,
    "text": "Barack Obama met leaders from European Union in Geneva, Switzerland to discuss policy announcement.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Barack Obama",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "European Union",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "Geneva",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Switzerland",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 353,
    "text": "The battle marked a turning point in Rome, Italy's history.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Rome",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Italy",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 354,
    "text": "A bill passage was passed by Parliament impacting Geneva, Switzerland.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Parliament",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "Geneva",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Switzerland",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 355,
    "text": "A bill passage was passed by Congress impacting New Delhi, India.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Congress",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "New Delhi",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "India",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 356,
    "text": "Cristiano Ronaldo led Team India to victory at the tournament in Madrid, Spain.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Cristiano Ronaldo",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "Team India",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "Madrid",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Spain",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 357,
    "text": "The uprising took place in Rome, Italy and involved Roman Senate.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Rome",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Italy",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Roman Senate",
        "NORP"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 358,
    "text": "NBA announced a new final match for 2022-2023.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "NBA",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "2022-2023",
        "DATE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 359,
    "text": "The coronation took place in Delhi, India and involved Roman Senate.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Delhi",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "India",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Roman Senate",
        "NORP"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 360,
    "text": "M.S. Dhoni led NBA to victory at the season opener in Melbourne, Australia.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "M.S. Dhoni",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "NBA",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "Melbourne",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Australia",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 361,
    "text": "Marie Curie published findings on climate study at Harvard University.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Marie Curie",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "Harvard University",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 362,
    "text": "Rachel Carson led trials of irrigation technique adoption in Punjab, India.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Rachel Carson",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "Punjab",
        "NORP"
      ],
      [
        "India",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 363,
    "text": "A study on gene sequencing led by Albert Einstein was published on 1960-05-22.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Albert Einstein",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "1960-05-22",
        "DATE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 364,
    "text": "Vincent van Gogh exhibited a new opera at Louvre Museum.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Vincent van Gogh",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "Louvre Museum",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 365,
    "text": "Kamala Harris announced policy changes regarding education at Washington, USA.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Kamala Harris",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "Washington",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "USA",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 366,
    "text": "The final match in Melbourne, Australia featured Serena Williams and Team India.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Melbourne",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Australia",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Serena Williams",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "Team India",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 367,
    "text": "Siemens acquired Tesla in a deal valued at $15M.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Siemens",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "Tesla",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "15M.",
        "MONEY"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 368,
    "text": "IBM released a AI-driven sensors that improves quantum computing.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "IBM",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "AI",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 369,
    "text": "Metropolitan Opera announced restoration of the symphony in New York, USA.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Metropolitan Opera",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "New York",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "USA",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 370,
    "text": "Sundar Pichai became CEO of Goldman Sachs following the acquisition.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Sundar Pichai",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "Goldman Sachs",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 371,
    "text": "Leonardo da Vinci exhibited a new installation at Sydney Opera House.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Leonardo da Vinci",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "Sydney Opera House",
        "ORG"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 372,
    "text": "Serena Williams led Team India to victory at the tournament in Madrid, Spain.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Serena Williams",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "Team India",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "Madrid",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Spain",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 373,
    "text": "Rachel Carson led trials of yield improvement study in Nairobi, Kenya.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Rachel Carson",
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        "Nairobi",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Kenya",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 374,
    "text": "The Treaty signing took place in Constantinople, Turkey and involved Mughal Empire.",
    "entities": [
      [
        "Treaty",
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        "Constantinople",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Turkey",
        "GPE"
      ],
      [
        "Mughal Empire",
        "GPE"
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 375,
